Aaliyah learned that she needed to define a realistic purpose
for the time that was given for the meeting.
Not everything can get accomplished in 30 minutes or an hour.
And it’s actually really important, practically speaking, that we don’t try to stuff everything and the kitchen sink into one meeting.
It’s important to define your purpose
clearly, and make sure that you are being realistic about what can be achieved in a given time frame.
It’s much better to have a clear and well-directed purpose,
where people come into the meeting understanding
what is happening, and leave the meeting with a clear set of actions and commitments.
You can always set up an additional meeting, or a meeting at a later time, to cover other topics.
But trying to do too much in one meeting is just a recipe for disaster.